ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE



32 years old

CONTACT

⊠ arnaudRsene@gmail.com

1+33 6 48 01 28 14

♀ France

ABOUT ME

I'm an Account Executive who spent nearly 10 years working on all aspects of the sales cycle across multiple industries.

My sales mindset is simple: as CEO of my territory, I'm accountable to find potential customers, close prospects and grow new accounts. It allows me to make adjustments in order to be consistent in time and deliver the number

I also believe a good Account
Executive has to be a good
quarterback. Managing a lot of
moving parts (internal
ecosystem of ressources /
partner etc) to keep the velocity
necessary to convert a sales
opportunity. In the life of a
deal, a million things can go
wrong and my job is to be able
to identify those issues,
understand them, and fix them.

After building and handling the Financial Services vertical for the Salesforce French market for four years and accomplishing the goals I had set, I decided to take a break to travel and think about what kind of next steps I wanted. After 18 months (Covid-19 added more months than anticipated), I'm recharged and ready to take on a new challenge.

EXPERIENCE

Sabbatical

Life inc. - Since April 2019 - Paris

- Time-off to reset mentally
- ▶ Travel : Canada / Senegal / France
- Health: Nutrition / Brazilian Jiu Jitsu
- Online Poker

Account Executive

Salesforce - April 2015 to April 2019 - Dublin



- Hired by the RVP Europe to build and grow the Financials Services vertical for the French ESMB market. Inbound and outbound strategy for:
- Traditional Financial Services (Asset Management & Wealth Management / Private Equity & Venture Capital / Insurance Brokers)
- Fintech
- ▶ Grew AOV from 500K\$/year to 6M\$/year

Account Manager

Citron - May 2014 to April 2015 - Paris



- Inbound: Up Sell / Cross Sell & RFPs
- Outbound : Lagardère / Master Contract Agreement (300k\$/year)

Account Executive

FDV Partner - May 2012 to May 2014 - Paris



Citron

- Startup specialized in business developpement. In charge of sourcing business opportunities for a portfolio of three customers: 99 Partners (Finance) / Kyu Associés (Management) / LesMobilizers (Mobile Apps)
- Identify and engage potential high value targets (C-Level)
- Driving the sales cycle until the deal is closed
- Reporting to initial customer
- Onboarding and coaching of new hires (FDV internal)

Co-Founder

Esport Betting League - January 2011 to January 2012 - Mountain View



- Website dedicated to betting on Esport competitions (Starcraft II & League of Legends)
- ▶ Technical project developpement
- Digital Marketing strategy (Google & Facebook adds)
- Customer Service

EDUCATION

City University

London

2009 to 2010

Master of Science in Telecoms & Networks

Ecole Centrale d'Electronique (ECE)

Paris

2006 to 2009

Engineering School

SKILLS

Data Driven

Rely on numbers to craft the best sales strategy

Consistency

Consistency comes from strong forecast accuracy

Organisation / Time Management

Prioritize daily tasks in order to maximise returns

Coaching / Onboarding

Enable people with the best practices and give them the tools to perform

Trust

Pretty straightforward

Emotional Intelligence

Management of emotions in high pressure moments

Knowledge / Business Acumen

Technical background allowing me to consume and retain information

CRM

Pipedrive / Hubspot / Salesforce

INTERESTS

Hobbies

- Music
- Poker
- Esport
- NBA
- Travel
- Crypto Currencies